(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Hey everybody!
Today, I would like to introduce you...
...to the one, the only entertainer,
Lady Riona!
始まったショータイム
The showtime has begun!
鳴り響く歓声
Echoing cheers!
Let's get up, let's get up, let's...
お嬢がじゃんかじゃんか
The young lady's shamisen strumming...
心を躍らせ
...makes your heart dance!
Let's get up, let's get up, let's...
Whoa, oh, oh!
耳を鳴らせば
If you snap your fingers...
変わりだす景色は
...the scenery begins to change.
フェイクだとしてもホログラム
Even if it's a fake hologram,
今宵の主役は私よ
tonight's main character is me!
1, 2, Let's go see, go!
It's my show time!
Let the show begin, 最高のショー
Let the show begin, the greatest show!
楽しむのさ、この瞬間
Let's enjoy this moment!
一度きりの人生、あとはダーリン、ダーリン、ダーリン、Yeah!
You only live once, after that, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も、仕事も
Whether it's love, or work,
一切合切 飲み干そう
let's drink it all up!
1, 2, 3, 4, Whoa
Let the show begin!
照らすムーンライト、スポットライトにして
Make the shining moonlight my spotlight.
Let's get up, let's get up, let's...
踊れ、ラッタッタ
Dance, rat-tat-tat,
軽快なステップで
with light and nimble steps.
Let's get up, let's get up, let's...
Whoa, oh, oh!
音を鳴らせば
If you play a sound,
拍手の渦が
a whirlpool of applause...
届くのさ、今宵の主役はあなたも
...will reach you, tonight's main character is also you!
1, 2, Let's go see, go!
It's our show time!
Let the show begin, 最高のショー
Let the show begin, the greatest show!
楽しむのさ、この瞬間
Let's enjoy this moment!
一度きりの人生、あとはダーリン、ダーリン、ダーリン、Yeah!
You only live once, after that, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も、仕事も
Whether it's love, or work,
一切合切 飲み干そう
let's drink it all up!
1, 2, 3, 4, Whoa
Let the show begin!
Ha-ha-ha! Come on, trombone!
Oh, oh!
Yeah!
Oh...
Show me your love, everybody, come on follow me, yeah!
Dance till the last...
今宵も
Tonight, too...
Let's do it, baby, baby, baby, baby!
So beautiful
何度でも
Over and over again
Let's work it very very very very very!
Let the show begin!
あなたも...
You too...
...燃え尽きましょう
...let's burn it up!
一度きりの人生でしょ
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, right?
Darling darling darling yeah!
恋も...
Both love...
...仕事も...
...and work...
...いいじゃん
...aren't they great?
私のために
Just for me!
One, two, three, four, ha!
Let the show begin.
Let the show begin, 最高のshow
Let the show begin, the ultimate show
楽しんじゃいましょう
Let's enjoy it to the fullest
一度きりの人生なんだから
Since it's a once-in-a-lifetime life
Darling darling darling yeah!
恋も...
Both love...
...仕事も...
...and work...
...いいじゃん
...aren't they great?
私のために
Just for me!
One, two, three, four, ha!
This is my show time.
Be Naked
[Title: Be Naked]
I'm breaking down なて不可避 wanna be...
I'm breaking down, it's inevitable, I wanna be...
...他の誰でもないの me
...I'm none other than myself.
君の願いも簡単に叶えたから look at me
Because I easily granted your wish, look at me.
Make it
嘘だらけの世界とは break up
Break up with this world full of lies.
I wish, no filter
ありのままで描く the future
Drawing the future just as I am.
見え透いた嘘なら いらない
I don't need transparent lies.
もう二度と 間違わない
I will never make a mistake again.
こだわる my style, 譲れない
Sticking to my style, I won't give in.
超えていく my life, right now
I'm rising above in my life, right now.
自由に my life, 見せるだけ
Living my life freely, I'll show you.
振り向かない
I won't look back.
見せてよ Luxury
Show me your luxury.
満ち足りて 駆け出す my world
Fully satisfied, running out into my world.
見せつける Ecstasy
Showing off ecstasy.
Don't play, I don't care, だから
Don't play, I don't care, so...
...go my way
...I'll go my way.
Show me without a filter
Be naked
ただ望むままに get it
Just get it as you desire.
We naked
Show me without a filter
Do you understand?
We're badass, we must stay, ただ望むままに get it
We're badass, we must stay, just get it as you desire.
No more lies, be my girls
We're badass, I know that, だから遠慮はしない
We're badass, I know that, so I won't hold back.
手放せない handle, 走るから run boy
Can't let go of the handle, because I'm running, run boy.
惑わせる Fantasy
Bewildering fantasy.
もう二度と 騙されはしないの
I will never be fooled again.
幕開ける Finally
It's finally starting.
I'm okay, I'm okay, だから
I'm okay, I'm okay, so...
...don't be afraid
Show me without a filter
Be naked
ただ望むままに get it
Just get it as you desire.
We naked
Show me without a filter
自分隠すのは楽だよね
It's easy to hide yourself, isn't it?
周りに合わせていればそれで...
If you just go along with others...
...とりあえず一人にならずに済むから Alright
...for now, you can avoid being alone, alright?
でも本当はもう気づいてる
But deep down, you already know.
胸の奥底にうずいてる
It's aching deep in your heart.
なのになんで諦めてる
So why are you giving up?
もう一度確かめて
Check one more time.
始めましょう リアルな show
Let's begin, the real show.
どこからでも好きにどうぞ
Help yourself from wherever you like.
I don't hide, Show me without a filter!
Hey! What you want?
Tell me please, don't be shy.
Hey! What you need?
大丈夫さ
It's alright.
Hey! What you want?
Tell me please, don't be shy.
そのままで get it on
Just get it on as you are.
Make it true.
Hey! What you want?
Tell me please, don't be shy.
Hey! What you need?
大丈夫さ
It's alright.
Hey! What you want?
Tell me please, don't be shy.
そのままで get it on
Just get it on as you are.
Make it true.
「ユルサナイ」
"I won't forgive you"
ゾッとした表情が可愛いね
Your terrified expression is so cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
love it？ ナニにラリって
Love it? What are you high on?
愛 high 可哀想ね
Love high, how pitiful.
ずっと下向いた顔が可愛いな
Your face looking down all the time is so cute
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours
ラヴィ何？ 割と愛 ハイハイ
Lovi what? Relatively love, yes, yes
可哀想ね 君は悪い子なの？
How pitiful, are you a bad child?
どの子がお好きで サニサニ
Which girl do you like? Sunny, sunny
色目やお上手でたわむれ
Flirting so skillfully, just playing around
君に踊らされちゃって私は狂う
Being danced around by you, I'm going crazy
What is loveit?
君のなかまで 骨の髄まで
Deep inside you, to the very marrow of your bones
いれてからあとになる愛のパペット
After putting it in, you become a puppet of love
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest feels tight, doesn't it? You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha
ずるい声で ほら囁いて
Come on, whisper to me with that sly voice
いい子ね 首輪はつけた？君はラヴィ
Good child. Did you put on the collar? You are Lovi
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone mad, haven't you? Love is blind, after all
したいようにしてあげるわ いつまで
I'll let you do whatever you want, forever
濡れた君の赤い脊髄 汚れるまで
Until your wet, red spinal cord is stained
痛いの飛んでいけ 死んでラヴィになるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until you die and become Lovi
愚かね 愚かね 間抜けな顔して君は悪い子なの
How foolish, how foolish, with that blank face, you're a bad child
痛いのがお好きで サニサニ
So you like pain? Sunny, sunny
あらお口はチャックで何々
My, zip your mouth shut, what's what
君に踊らされちゃう君は狂う
Danced around, you also go crazy
What is...
君のなかまで 骨の髄まで
Deep inside you, to the very marrow of your bones
しゃぶりつくせばもう空っぽのパペット
Once sucked dry, you're just an empty puppet
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest feels tight, doesn't it? You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて
You're a clown, aren't you? Whisper love to me
人間の形した君はラヴィ
You, who took a human shape, are Lovi
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone mad, haven't you? Love is blind, after all
したいようにしてあげるわ いつまで
I'll let you do whatever you want, forever
報い尽くせない汚れ達に溺れるまで
Until you drown in sins that can never be paid back
痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until your breath stops
報い尽くせない汚れ達に溺れるまで
Until you drown in sins that can never be paid back
痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until your breath stops
お待たせー！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
本日は、伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026に遊びに来てくれて、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Isaki Riona's Birthday Festival 2026 today!
Let's the show begin、えっと、V、きっと、ラヴィと、3曲続けて披露させていただきました！
I just performed three songs in a row: 'Let's the show begin', 'V', and 'Lovi'!
どうですかー？
What do you think?!
改めて自己紹介させてください！
Please let me introduce myself once again!
私の元に、おいで！
Come to me!
リオナ・イン・ザ・ステージ！
Riona on the stage!
FLOWGLOWのリーダー、伊咲リオナです！プロー！
I'm the leader of FLOWGLOW, Isaki Riona! Flow-!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
はぁ、息切れが、息切れがヤバいんですけど...
Phew, I'm so, so out of breath...
はい、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはこちら！
Anyway, today's hashtag is this!
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026です！
Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026!
たくさん、たくさん、呟いてください！
Please tweet a lot, a lot!
私、絶対見に行くのでね！
Because I will definitely go check them out!
みんなが、感想とか、送ってくれるの、すごく楽しみにしています！
I'm really looking forward to everyone sending thoughts and feedback!
そしてですね...
And also...
本日、ライブパフォーマンスさせていただくステージは、こちらです！
This is the stage where I'll be performing live today!
どうですかー？
How do you like it?!
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない？
It feels like a show, isn't it awesome?
あとね、伊咲リオナっていうね、名前がたくさん刻まれていたり...
And look, the name 'Isaki Riona' is engraved all over...
ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり...
with heart balloons, crowns...
いろんな装飾があって、とってもキラキラしてます！
and various decorations, it's so sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが今日すごくすごく幸せです！ありがとうございます！
I'm so, so happy to be dancing here today! Thank you so much!
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが「THE ONE AND ONLY」となっております！
And the title of today's live is 'THE ONE AND ONLY'!
こちらの意味は、「唯一無二」という意味です！
This means 'the one and only' or 'unique'!
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので...
To live up to this title, I will perform with all my might...
どうかこの時間が、あなたの心に何か届けられる、そんな時間になれるように...
so I hope this can be a moment that delivers something to your heart...
今日は頑張りたいと思います！
I'll do my absolute best today!
それでは次は、おまちかねのゲストパートです！
Now next up is the long-awaited guest part!
どうぞ！
Here we go!
Blah Blah VIRTUAL Blah Blah
I'm a B...
I'm a B... La Vida La Vida La Vida Love... blah blah blah
たかだかノーマルな混沌
At most, just a normal chaos
さわらばかわいいのこと
If you touch it, it's a cute thing
高天原からほら
Look, from Takamagahara
戻してあげる
I'll bring you back
Hi, そう メンヘラ
Hi, yes, a mental health case
お面がキュートならメンキラー
If the mask is cute, a men-killer
とか貼られた レッテル イッてる メンタル
Labels like that being stuck on, an insane mental state
は？
Huh?
最狂 スマイルで
With the craziest smile
転がしてく ペンペン
Rolling them over, pen-pen
誤魔化してる正真正銘 晒されたら バイバイ
Deceiving, genuine and true, if exposed, then bye-bye
なんてな
Just kidding
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a V...
I am...
La Vida La Vida La Vida...
夢見てる少年
Dreaming boys...
夢見てる少女へ
To dreaming girls...
Vだ、Vだ、Vは 甘々甘々脳
V, V, V is a sweet, sweet brain
刺激 ギギ ギギ も そう
Stimulation, -tion, -tion, -tion is also like that
我を忘れて
Losing yourself...
センター
Center
誰よりも客寄せのパンダ
A crowd-pulling panda more than anyone else
我らはなんだ
What are we?
まるで生んだ自己愛性勝者
Like a born narcissist winner
Am I V? 甘え
Am I V? Sweetness
甘え 甘し
Sweet, sugary
アライザライ 甘し
Sweet all over
ソライに
To the sky
お互いに
To each other
So Love Me
おいでませ ヘイ モンスター
Welcome, hey monster
My name is Blah Blah
乱れたら儚き Laughter
If disordered, it's a fleeting laughter
甘い Bitter のバター
Sweet and bitter butter
心ん中 Smooth like Butter
Inside my heart, smooth like butter
Touch me したいならほら円だ
If you want to touch me, look, it's yen
Catch me でハイピース
Catch me and high peace
召しあがる主食は分からないが
I don't know what staple food you eat but...
心叫ぶ
...my heart screams
一つも Lifer
Not even one lifer
生きる姿や魂を今
The way we live, our souls, now
二つにして愛をバラバラに
Split them in two and scatter love to pieces
生まれた時の喜びは ポーションに サヨナラでいいな
The joy of being born turned into a potion, a simple goodbye will do
ダメね
No good, is it?
Wacha Wacha
Wacha は Mecha Mecha?
Is Wacha all messy?
Wacha Wacha
Wacha は Mecha Mecha?
Is Wacha all messy?
楽観な濾過ね
Optimistic filtering
あらら好感で共感ね
Oh my, empathy through a favorable impression
怪体な正体ね あら
A bizarre true identity, oh
Wacha は Mecha Mecha?
Is Wacha all messy?
楽観な濾過ね
Optimistic filtering
あらら共感で好感ね
Oh my, favorable impression through empathy
一巻の終わりだね
That's the end of the chapter
I'm the Diva
I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, あわ、あわ、あわよ
I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, bubbly, bubbly, bubble
I'm a, La Vida I am Diva 淫らは嫌よ
I'm a, La Vida I am Diva, I hate being lewd
夢見ている少年
The dreaming boy
夢見ている少女へ
To the dreaming girl
Diva な Diva は 甘々甘々なの
A Diva-like Diva is super, super sweet
そういうお年頃
That's the age we're at
子供の頃言われたもんだ あのヒーローショーの人形の
I was told when I was a kid, that hero show doll's...
背中にはチャックは付いてないから開くな
...back doesn't have a zipper, so don't open it
バーチャルだヒューマンだ四の五の言うな
Virtual or human, don't complain about this and that
存在はワンワンダー
Our existence is a wonder
褒めても惚れても死の後バラバラな
Even if praised or loved, after death we're in pieces
Virtual Blah Blah Blah Virtual Blah Blah
That's not any fun.
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah.
That's karma.
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah.
That's karma, ha ha ha.
想像から創造 衝動から猛攻
From imagination to creation, from impulse to onslaught.
ほらあっという間に華麗に変身 変幻自在
Look, in the blink of an eye, a gorgeous transformation, ever-changing.
毒々しい本能
A poisonous instinct.
喰らえ咆哮
Taste my roar.
Sorry I'm just better.
Sorry we're go-getters.
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever, whatever! Talk about a "kumbaya".
Isekai queen, switch tuning minor.
Colorful ni cacophony 歪で優雅に
Colorful cacophony, distorted and elegant.
ハチャメチャ Welcome to miss fortune's game.
Absurdity, welcome to Miss Fortune's game.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
カリオペ先輩！来てくれてありがとうございました！
Calliope-senpai! Thank you so much for coming!
Yeah! 楽しかった！また歌いましょう！
Yeah! It was so much fun! Let's sing together again!
はい！また歌いましょう！
Yes! Let's sing together again!
また歌いましょう！
Let's sing together again!
歌いましょう！
Let's sing!
チュチュチュ！ / チュチュ！
Chu chu chu! / Chu chu!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!
カルテNo.2222
(作詞：nobara kaede / 作曲：金山秀士 (Dream Monster))
[Song: Karte No. 2222
Lyrics: nobara kaede / Composition: Shuji Kanayama (Dream Monster)]
あー…
Ah...
2-2-2-2
Kyu Kyu
Doom Doom Doom
2-2-2-2
Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru
Kyu
2-2-2-2
Burn Burn
Chu Chu
Open Your Karte
救助不可能
Beyond rescue,
恋の病なの
I'm lovesick.
どんどん熱を上げていく
My temperature keeps rising,
Virus
Love me
危険な魔法を
Try testing...
試してみる？
this dangerous magic?
Twinkle
Blink
飽くまで天使の誘惑
To the very end, an angel's temptation.
Heaven in hell
ドキドキ
Thump-thump,
動機は純粋
my motive is pure.
甘い
Sweet,
甘い乙女心
sweet maiden's heart.
どっちどっち
Which way, which way?
さあ 手の平の迷宮へようこそ
Come, welcome to the labyrinth in the palm of my hand.
「いい子だね」
“Good child.”
カルテNo.
Karte No.
運命の
Our destined
2 2
鳴り止まない
It won't stop ringing,
サイレン音が
the sound of the siren,
Wee Woo Wee Woo
好き 好き 填まる 愛の心電図
Love, love, falling into this electrocardiogram of love.
はい、お薬をどうぞ
Here is your medicine.
To to to
2-2-2-2
Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru
Doom Doom Doom Doom
2-2-2-2
Kyu
Zoom
2-2-2-2
Kyu Kyu
Burn Burn Burn
2-2-2-2
Chu Chu Chu
Open Your Karte
24時間
24 hours,
呼吸困難
difficulty breathing.
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして
Kiss the thorns of a crimson rose,
Kiss me
麻酔みたいな台詞
lines like anesthesia,
魔性のBaby face
devilish baby face.
籠で飛び交う青い鳥
Bluebirds flying in a cage.
Try & Error
ドクドク
Thumping,
毒みたいな愛
a love like poison.
Blink
笑顔に落とす前
Before dropping it on your smile,
チクタク
Tick-tock,
もう時間がない 秘密の正体
there's no more time, the true nature of the secret.
「悪い子かも♡」
“Maybe I'm a bad girl.”
カルテNo.
Karte No.
運命の
Our destined
2 2
追い付けない
You can't catch up,
超スピードで
at super speed.
Wee Woo Wee Woo
ズキズキ乱れる 愛の心電図
A throbbing, disordered electrocardiogram of love.
もう重症みたいです
It seems you're already in critical condition.
Too too too Me
先生！緊急事態です！
Doctor! It's an emergency!
カルテNo.2222の患者様です！
It's the patient of Karte No. 2222!
見てください！心電図がハートの形になってます！
Look! The electrocardiogram is shaped like a heart!
もしもーし、聞こえますかー？
Hello? Can you hear me?
えっ？「可愛すぎて胸が苦しい、息ができない」？
Eh? "Too cute, my chest hurts, I can't breathe"?
もっと好きになっちゃう注射しましょうね♪
Let me give you a shot to make you love me even more♪
大丈夫ですよー、ずっと私が手を握っていますからね♪
It's okay, I'll hold your hand the entire time♪
あーあ、だから言ったのに！
Ah, I told you so!
カルテNo.
Karte No.
さあ選んで 4 Card
Now choose, 4 of a Card,
見上げて あの夜空に
I looked up at that night sky,
浮かぶ星たち
And the stars floating there.
ふっと君の声が
Suddenly, I heard your voice...
あの頃 輝いてたかな
Was it shining back then?
今になっては
Now that it's come to this,
ずっと わからないまま
I'll never know.
オーケストラ
作詞: JxSxK / 松隈ケンタ  作曲: 松隈ケンタ
[Song: Orchestra / Lyrics: JxSxK, Kenta Matsukuma / Composition: Kenta Matsukuma]
あの時
Back then,
君がついた嘘
The lie you told,
問いただせずに泣いたあの坂道
I couldn't question it, crying on that hill.
この先
From here on,
君と会えないの？
Will I never see you again?
離れ離れに身を任せていた
I had resigned myself to our being apart.
いつもの後悔が 風に消えてく
My usual regrets are vanishing in the wind.
誰にも見せないその姿を
The side of you that you'd never show anyone else,
もう少しだけ見ていたかったんだ
I wanted to see it just a little more.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is silently glaring at us.
その手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
笑い合っていた声 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the voices of us laughing together.
こんなにも流してた
All these tears that were flowing,
涙も 語る声も
Even the tears and speaking voices,
オーケストラ
Are an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
It eventually came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the voice of goodbye.
あんまりにも近くにいたはずだ
We should have been so close,
今では繋がりなんて
But now, our only connection
あの空だけ
Is that sky above.
夜空の言葉にしよう
Let's put it into words of the night sky.
馬鹿らしくなって投げた午前3時
Getting silly, we threw away that 3 AM.
これから先
From here on,
君と何年も
Even years with you,
時の流れに身を任せても
Even if I leave myself to the flow of time,
いつものジョークが街に消えてく
Our usual jokes are vanishing into the city.
誰にも見せない僕の姿を
My side that I'd never show anyone else,
もう少しだけ見せたかったんだ
I wanted to show you just a little more.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is silently glaring at us.
この目と目合わせて
With our eyes meeting,
はっきりとしたい
I want to make it clear,
もうできないかな
I guess I can't do that anymore.
こんなにも遠く近くで辛いのを
It hurts so much to be so far, yet so close,
音奏でる オーケストラ
As the orchestra plays its sound.
どこで何をしてるの
Where are you now, what are you doing?
わからないのは
The fact that I don't know...
僕のせいなんだね
Is my fault, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日が来るなんて
That days like this would last forever,
神様いたずらなら呪いたいぐらい
If this is God's prank, I want to curse Him.
その手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
笑い合っていた声 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the voices of us laughing together.
こんなにも流してた
All these tears that were flowing,
涙も 語る声も オーケストラ
Even the tears and speaking voices, are an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
It eventually came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the voice of goodbye.
忘れはしないよ
I won't forget...
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
...how close we were supposed to be,
今では繋がりなんて
but now, our only connection...
この空だけ
...is this sky.
Wow oh
Wow oh oh oh...
せーの！
Ready, go!
リオナ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Riona, happy birthday!
ありがとう！なんとFlow Glowのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Thank you! Everyone from Flow Glow actually came! Thank you!
やったー！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
はい、ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで。そしてFlow Glowでね、こうやってライブできて、すごく嬉しいよ！
Yes, finally, my first birthday live. And performing like this with Flow Glow, I'm so happy!
呼んでくれてありがとう！おめでとう！
Thank you for inviting us! Congratulations!
エモかったね。めっちゃエモかった！
That was so emotional. Super emotional!
どうですか？エモかったですか？
What do you think? Was it emotional?
泣いちゃったよ、リオナちゃん。泣いちゃった、泣いちゃった。
I almost cried, Riona-chan. I really did!
みんなでこうやってね、まぁ、みんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうか、まぁ分かんないんだけど...
Doing this together... well, I don't know if everyone will get a birthday live...
え、どうだろ？Flow Glowになってまだ2ヶ月しか経ってないの！
I wonder? It's only been two months since Flow Glow started!
うちらも察してよ！リーダー、出させてくれて本当にありがとうございました！
Think about us too! Leader, thank you so much for letting us perform!
いやいや、一応リーダーとしてね、お仕事しておきました！
No, no, as the leader, I had to do my job!
ということで、今日は誕生日プレゼントに、みんなからの超絶可愛い『おめでとう、リオナおめでとう！』っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけど、いいかな？
So, as a birthday gift today, I'd like a super-cute 'Happy birthday, Riona!' from everyone as a present, would that be okay?
いいですよ！誕生日ですしね！もちろん！
Sure! It is your birthday after all! Of course!
プレゼントもらっていいですか？おめでとう！みたいなやつ。
Can I have my present? A 'Happy birthday!' kind of thing.
じゃあ、『せーの』って言ったら、『リオナ、おめでとう』って言ってね。オッケー？プレゼントね、プレゼント。
So, when I say 'ready, go,' please say 'Riona, happy birthday.' Okay? This is my present, okay?
プレゼントならしょうがないな。ちゃんと可愛くやれよ！可愛くね！
If it's a present, we have no choice. Do it properly and cutely! Cutely, okay!
せーの！
Ready, go!
リオナー！！！
Rionaaa!!!
ちょっと待って！もっと可愛い声で！何それ！
Wait a minute! Use a cuter voice! What was that?!
じゃあ見本見せてよ、見本！
Then show us an example!
初めての生誕祭なんだから、愛の言葉的なさ...セクシーで可愛くて愛。
It's your first birthday festival, so how about some words of love... sexy, cute, and full of love.
オッケー、行きますよ。リオナからの愛の言葉。3、2、1、はい！
Okay, here I go. Words of love from Riona. 3, 2, 1, go!
今年も、来年も、再来年も、あなたに祝ってもらえますように。
This year, next year, and the year after... I hope you'll always be there to celebrate with me.
キャーーー！すごーーい！可愛い！
Kyaaa! Amazing! So cute!
あなたは、お残りです。
You're staying behind.
まるで この世界で
It's as if in this world...
二人きりみたいだね
...we are the only two here.
だって 少しだけ
Because, just a little...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...I ended up dreaming.
爪先に 月明かり
Moonlight on my toes,
花束の香りに
the scent of a bouquet...
指に触れる憂い
...and sorrow touching my fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I must go now,
何もかも忘れて
forgetting everything.
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on glass,
痛む毎に 血が流れて落ちていく
with every painful step, blood flows and drips away.
お願い その赤い 足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come to meet me.
錆びたプールに 放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusty pool.
言葉を喉の奥 隠した林檎
An apple that hid words deep in its throat.
しなびた君の肌に 残る傷は遠く
The scars remaining on your withered skin are far away.
...のように泳いだ迷子
...like a lost child swimming.
「どこにいる？」「どこにいるよ」
"Where are you?" "I'm right here."
「何をしてる？」「ずっと見てるよ」
"What are you doing?" "I'm always watching you."
場所間違えて満たそう
Let's fill it up, even if it's the wrong place.
そばにいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこを見るの？
Where are you looking?
硝子のうえを裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of glass,
痛む毎に血が流れて落ちていく
With every pain, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints,
会いに来て
And come to see me.
まあるいこの世界で
In this round world...
二人だけみたいだね
...it's like there's only the two of us.
なんて
Just...
少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
...I was only dreaming for a little while.
なんて...
Just...
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Stinging my cheeks, the morning Yamate Street,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away the empty cigarette box.
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Again today, there is no place to step,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
My small room spoils my loneliness.
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love the unsettling screams,
破るドイツ車と
...German car breaking...
パトカー
...and patrol car.
サイレン
Siren...
爆音
...roar...
現実界
...reality...
或る浮遊
...a certain levitation.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love the restless screams,
未来等見ないで
don't look at the future or anything,
確信出来る現在だけ
layer only the present I can be certain of,
重ねて
over and over.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ
recognize only this as necessary,
認めて
accept me.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love the restless screams!
確信出来る現在だけ
Layer only the present I can be certain of,
重ねて
over and over.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ
recognize only this as necessary,
認めて
accept me.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
The morning Yamate Street that stabs my cheeks,
烟草の空き箱を捨てる
throwing away an empty cigarette box.
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Again today there is no room for my feet,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
a small room indulges in solitude...
ねえ あんた答えてよ
Hey, answer me!
誰そ彼 お手元の世界に夢中
Someone is absorbed in the world in their hands,
化け物の飼い方を学んでる
learning how to keep a monster.
選ばれる為なら舌を売る
Selling their tongue if it means being chosen,
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
digging a grave only as much as they've been betrayed.
へらへらのおつむがどうにかして
Their foolish head does something,
うすら寒い言葉ばかりになる
and it all turns into chilling words.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If I could say bye-bye to faces I don't remember,
阿修羅にだってなれるわ保存
I could even become an Ashura!
逃げるえすけいぷえすけいぷえすけいぷ 仏のまま
Running, escape escape escape, as Buddha is,
飛べるすてっぷすてっぷすてっぷ 仰せのまま
flying, step step step, as ordered.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Whoa there, even devouring Enma the King of Hell!
騙るすにーくすにーくすにーく 嵐の中
Sneaking, sneak sneak sneak, in the storm,
跳ねるすきっぷすきっぷすきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
skipping, skip skip skip, oh well, piece of cake.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Just go ahead and suck until the marrow of the bone!
ねえ あんた答えてよ保存
Hey, answer me!
日々の滲みを木々に焼べて暖をとり合う
We burn our daily stains like firewood to warm each other,
ねえ ギャーギャー言っちゃって 頭を垂れないで！
Hey, keep screaming, don't bow your head!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
みんなありがとうー！
Thank you, everyone!
はぁ、やばい、ちょっと息が... お水飲ませてくださいね。すいませんね。
Phew, that was intense... Let me drink some water, okay? Sorry.
ふぅ、うまい。すいません、ありがとうございます。お待たせしてすいませんね。
Phew, that was good. Thank you, sorry about that. Sorry to keep you waiting.
えっと、先ほどは、「ベノム」と、「罪と罰」と、「阿修羅ちゃん」をお届けしました。いかがでしたでしょうか？
Let's see, earlier, I performed "Venom," "Crime and Punishment," and "Asura-chan." How did you like them?
この後も、まだまだライブは続きます！
The live performance will still continue after this!
まだ披露してない、あんな曲や、こんな曲が、あるかもね！
There might be that song, or this song, that I haven't performed yet!
なので、チャンネルはそのままで、まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
So, please keep the channel as it is and continue watching!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください！こちらです！
Now, please let me make an announcement to everyone! Here it is!
伊咲リオナ誕生日記念2026のグッズが出ます！やったー！
Isaki Riona Birthday Commemoration 2026 merchandise is coming out! Yay!
では、詳細を、見ていきましょう！まずは、こちらです！
Now, let's take a look at the details! First up is this!
「RIONA ON THE ステージタペストリー」！
"RIONA ON THE Stage Tapestry"!
イラストは今回、明春先生にお願いさせていただきました！
We asked Akiharu-sensei to draw the illustration this time!
ライブ中のリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、とっても可愛いイラストになっているので、タペストリーでぜひ堪能してください！
With the theme of Riona during her live performance, it's a very cute illustration, so please enjoy it on the tapestry!
2つ目は、こちら！
Second is this!
「リオナとおそろいネックレス」！
"Riona's Matching Necklace"!
真ん中には王冠のデザイン、周りには伊咲リオナのロゴが入っています。シンプルになってますのでね、ぜひリオナとおそろいにしてくれたら嬉しいです！
It features a crown design in the center with Isaki Riona's logo around it. It's quite simple, so I'd be happy if you match with Riona!
次は、こちら！
Next is this!
「リオナのぬいをいれるポーチ」！
"Pouch to Put Riona's Plushie In"!
リオナっぽさ全開のぬいポーチになってます。
It's a plushie pouch packed with Riona's style.
ぜひ、リオナのぬいをいれてくれたら嬉しいなと思います。ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよ、ポーチになるよ。
I'd be happy if you put Riona's plushie inside. It's totally fine to use it for other things, too, as a regular pouch.
そしてそして、最後は、こちら！
And then, last but not least, is this!
「くしゃみ連発 ぬいキーホルダー」！
"Sneeze Barrage Plushie Keyring"!
今回、描き下ろしイラストの衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます。
This time, it's a plushie keyring in the outfit of the newly drawn illustration.
なんと、この手の部分をポチッと押すと、「ハックション！」と言うので、いっぱい押してね、いっぱい浴びてもらえればと思います！
If you press this hand part, it will sneeze "Achoo!", so please press it a lot and receive many sneezes!
そしたら、改めてね、フルセットの方を全部見ていきましょう。こちら！
Now, let's take a look at the full set again. Here!
盛りだくさん！もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります。こちら！
So many things! Of course, there are also full-set purchase bonuses. Here!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は、直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りのバックステージパス風カードです！
The first full-set purchase bonus is a backstage pass-style card with a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped message!
こちらも明春先生のイラストに、全て私がね、1つ1つ、心を込めてサインさせていただくので、よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
This also features Akiharu-sensei's illustration, and I will personally sign each and every one of them with all my heart, so please buy it if you'd like!
2つ目は、特典ボイス！
The second is the bonus voice!
「ライブ前に君と...」です。ライブ前にね、緊張してはわはわってなってるリオナを励ますシチュエーションとなっております。ぜひね、ボイスの方は聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
"With You Before the Live Performance." It's a situation where you encourage Riona, who is nervous and flustered before the live. I hope you'll listen to the voice!
こちらのグッズは、21時、9時からカートオープンです！みんなよかったらぜひぜひゲットしてください！
The cart opens for these goods at 21:00, 9 PM! Please get them if you'd like!
そして、大事なお知らせが2つ目、あります。聞いてください。
And we have a second important announcement. Please listen.
ドゥルルルルルルルル、ジャン！
(Drumroll) Ta-da!
伊咲リオナの、初、ソロの新曲が出ます！やったー！
Isaki Riona's first ever solo new song is coming out! Yay!
タイトルは、「Ring my name」です。こちら、私の思いだったり、これから先、どうやってこう進んでいくか、「私は進んでいくぞ」というのが、おしゃれで優雅にエレガントに表現された曲となっております。
The title is "Ring my name." This song is an elegant, stylish representation of my feelings, and how I will move forward—saying "I will move forward!"
こちらセクシーな振り付けもついているので、よかったらそこに注目してくださると嬉しいです！
It also features some sexy choreography, so I'd be happy if you pay attention to that!
この後、このライブが終わった後すぐにMVも公開されますし、この後24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、ぜひいっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
Right after this live ends, the MV will be released immediately, and from 24:00 today, it will be digitally released, so I'd be happy if you listen to it a lot!
やっぱり、この後は新曲やっちゃいますよね！
Of course, we have to perform the new song next!
ということでね、まあ、やっていくんですけど、その前にね、ちょっと語らせてくださいよ。まあね、リオナはね、まだまだなことがいっぱいあって、叶えたい夢もいっぱいあります。
So, we're going to do that, but before that, let me talk a little bit. You know, there are still many things I'm not good enough at, and there are many dreams I want to fulfill.
なので、まだまだ何も手にしてない私かもしれませんが、一緒に付いてきてくれたあなたと一緒に、いろんな夢だったり思い出を作っていきたいです。
So, I might still be someone who hasn't achieved anything yet, but together with you who followed me here, I want to make various dreams and memories.
絶対後悔はさせないんで、これからも私に付いてきてくれると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
I promise I won't make you regret it, so I hope you will continue to follow me. Thank you very much!
そしてこの後は、新曲の披露の前に、Variumの先輩方のオリ曲を使ったダンスメドレーをお届けします！
And up next, before performing the new song, we will deliver a dance medley using original songs from our Varium senpais!
ので、ぜひ見てください！
So please be sure to watch!
いくよ！心の準備できた？
Here we go! Are you ready?
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
I don't think about that. 楽しい？
I don't think about that. Is it fun?
My ruler is so fucking kawaii
かわいいね
How cute!
死神の先生、C'est la vie
Mr. Reaper, C'est la vie
素敵なアンサー
A wonderful answer
死神の仕事
A reaper's job
お楽しみに
Look forward to it
シャルイース
Shaluise
ビビディ・バビディ・ブー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo
I'm dressed in lace
甘い嘘は act
Sweet lies are an act
囁くの 'Want more?'
Whispering, 'Want more?'
吐息まで danger
Even my sighs are danger
Every step I take
心ごと奪って
Steal your very heart
Velvet shadows call my name
微熱は隠して
Hiding my slight fever
午前零時
Midnight...
今 Veilが解け
Now, the veil is undone
I'm breaking into the night
まだ夜は覚めやしない
The night won't end just yet
さあ、誰も彼も焦がれるままで
Come, while everyone is still yearning
私を見て
Look at me
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resound
今から Watch me right
From now on, watch me right
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, if I bloom in full glory
煌めく Ring
The sparkling ring
指先まで優雅に揺れる
Swaying gracefully down to my fingertips
鏡越しの操り人形
A marionette through the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
Smiling as if about to break
瞳の奥 falling low
Deep in my eyes, falling low
唇まで like a ghost
Even my lips are like a ghost
I can't stop 巡る走馬灯
I can't stop, a revolving kaleidoscope
さあ、魅せましょう 散るまで
Come, let me show you, until I scatter
綺麗な嘘で
With a beautiful lie
着飾らないのマスカレード
unadorned at the masquerade
Go ahead, keep deep promise
それならばいっそ Shall we dance
If so, we might as well... Shall we dance?
かませ Riona Riona Riona
Bring it on, Riona Riona Riona
Flavor only, no censor
今更 Bad, マーク, 連打, Bot
At this point, spamming Bad marks, Bots
やってられねーな等
I can't deal with this shit
I'm a wonder, can't look away, boy
魅せつけるの 全てを賭けて
I will show it off, risking everything
Are you ready?
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
微熱の中
In the slight fever
景色が溶けて
the scenery melts...
まだ夢は醒めない
The dream hasn't woken up yet.
To younger me, "you're alright"
名もなきあの頃に
To those nameless days:
「後悔はない」
"I have no regrets."
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resound!
今から紡ぐ未来
The future we spin from now on...
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now! If it blooms in full,
煌めくReina
the sparkling Queen!
明け方まで気高く踊る
Dancing proudly until dawn,
琥珀色のマスカレード
an amber-colored masquerade.
壊れそうに舞い乱れ...
Dancing wildly as if about to break!
Viva la reina
Cantar al alba
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resound!
今から紡ぐ未来
The future we spin from now on...
泡沫のティアラに
Enchanted by the fleeting tiara,
魅せられ
captivated,
ただ憧れ
just longing...
手を伸ばして
Stretching out my hand!
これからも私についてきてください！
Please keep following me from now on as well!
以上、響咲リオナでした！
That's all from Hibiki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
[画面メッセージ]
響咲リオナ生誕祭2026
お越しいただき、ありがとうございました！
[On-Screen Message]
Hibiki Riona Birthday Celebration 2026
Thank you for coming!
これからも皆さんとずっと一緒に居たい
貴方の居場所でありたい！
I want to be with you all forever...
I want to be a place where you belong!
お届けしたパフォーマンスが貴方の心に
少しでも何かを残せているといいな
I hope the performance I delivered
has left something in your heart, even if only a little.
本当に本当にありがとう！！
愛しています。
Thank you so, so much!!
I love you.